Are you seeing the things that are going
on in this world? Things that are
happening right now that are showing us
that time is short. We are not long for
this world, those of us who belong to
Jesus. And we're going to talk about
that today. We have so much to cover.
We'll also get to clown world, comments
of the day, question of the day, and all
the things we do here each day. My name
is Tom. You are watching the Watchman
River channel. Today is September 9th.
It's Wednesday, and uh it's a good day.
This is the day the Lord has made and we
will rejoice and be glad in it. I am uh
looking at my live studio audience right
now and it is two squirrels that are
playing and that's all I'm seeing today.
So, but that counts. That's a live
studio audience. But anyway, before we
get into the seriousness of our message,
I always like to read a few scriptures
from the word of God. I am in God's
promises for your every need. I'm on
page 94. What to do when you feel
condemned. Let's go to Romans 8:1. There
is therefore now no condemnation to
those who are in Christ Jesus, who do
not walk according to the flesh, but
according to the spirit.
Let's go to 2 Corinthians 5:1 17.
Therefore, if anyone is in Christ, he is
a new creation. Old things have passed
away. Behold, all things have become
new. Give me an amen, my friends. Thank
you. Let's go to John 3 17 and 18. For
God did not send his son into the world
to condemn the world, but that the world
through him might be saved. He who
believes in him is not condemned. But he
who does not believe is condemned
already because he has not believed in
the name of the only begotten son of
God. Oh my goodness. Do you know Jesus?
I I really hope you know Jesus. If you
don't, please keep watching this video
cuz you could have new life today, this
very day. John 5:4, most assuredly I say
to you, he who hears my word and
believes in him who sent me has
everlasting life and shall not come into
judgment, but has passed from death unto
life.
Let's go to Hebrews 8:12.
For I will be merciful to their
unrighteousness and their sins and their
lawless deeds. I will remember no more.
The most high God telling us he will not
remember our sins once we believe in the
atoning blood and gospel, the good news
of Jesus. Here's another one. Isaiah
43:25. Listen to this. I even I am he
who blotss out your transgressions for
my own sake and I will not remember your
sins. I mean that is amazing. Let's do
one more. Isaiah 55:7. Let the wicked
forsake his way and the unrighteous man
his thoughts. Let him return to the Lord
and he will have mercy on him and to our
God for he will abundantly pardon. These
are incredible
scriptures from the word of God. You
know when you belong to Jesus your
future is so amazing. But we sit here
right now in a world that is just super
perilous. But God, you know that Jesus
shines brighter and brighter the darker
this world gets. But I'll tell you right
now, this world is getting dark. It's
getting very dark. And I want to start
off here. It's a tweet that was well, I
don't know. I don't think they call them
tweets anymore, huh? We'll just call it
a post from X that was shared by, I
believe, uh, Amir Sarati, but I went
here and verified it. It is a a man who
recently resigned from Anthropic, which
is one of the biggest AI companies in
the world. Listen to what he said. His
name is Jacob Coxin. The people building
AI. Now, this guy just retired from
this, okay? He resigned from anthropic.
The people building AI earnestly believe
that it could kill us by the end of the
decade. Uh we are in 2026, late 2026.
The end of the decade is like three and
a half years away. Just interesting from
someone who just resigned from
anthropic.
This is not a marketing stunt, he said.
If anything, many executives and senior
researchers will couch their phrasing in
the press to sound sensible, but I hear
the same people express fear privately.
No other human activity poses this level
of danger. End of post.
Credible times when the creators of this
technology are saying they're afraid of
it, you know. But do they stop it? No.
They got to make their money. They got
to build their bunker so they can hide
from God during the seven-year
tribulation. They can hide in the rocks.
And they're all doing it. They're all
building bunkers.
Incredible times we're living in. And
we're seeing more and more of this stuff
and it's coming. I always say that Bible
prophecy is like the boulder that chases
Harrison Ford in the first Indiana Jones
movie. And I always say once that
boulder started the momentum chasing
him. It ain't going to roll back up that
hill. You know, that's the way I see
everything going on right now. I don't
see us, we're heading in, we're in
perilous times. We know that. But we
keep our eyes on Jesus. I just don't see
it getting better for a while and then
we reenter the last days. You know, I
think we're in the last days right now.
We're waiting for Jesus. We're not
naming a day or an hour. Many people are
naming days and hours. I won't do that.
I am waiting for Jesus because it's
God's perfect timing. It's not ours. And
I do believe it's an appointed time. I
do believe that God has known since
before the foundation of the world the
day he is going to say, "Son, go get
your bride." I think it is an appointed
time, but I don't think we're going to
figure it out. But anyway, look at this
one. Okay.
LG smart TVs caught logging audio with
screen off and snooping on local
devices. Do you have a TV? A new TV?
I'll tell you one thing. It's listening
to you even when you have it off.
An investigation by Gamers Nexus found
that LG smart TVs sweep local networks
to map phones and nearby devices. Test
also showed the sets can capture
microphone audio with the screen off.
They then upload data once reconnected
to the internet. So, it's listening to
you as you talk with the TV off and then
once it's on again and it's got the
Wi-Fi access, then it uploads it to
their servers. The data collection pool
is fed into the LG Ad Solutions, the
company's targeted advertising arm, and
LG claims they have roughly 216 million
smart TV sales globally. On the other
hand, the ad division says it has access
to, listen to this number, 363
million secondary addressable devices in
the US alone by tracking other hardware
on the same network.
You know, we always used to say, what's
going to happen with our privacy? We
knew in the last days privacy would be
gone, but oh my goodness, you know, your
television when it's off is listening to
you if you have a newer TV. You know, I
know Samsung, they've said that for
years. You know, some people are saying
that some TVs have cameras. Now, I can't
verify that. I'm not going to go that
far. I don't know. Wouldn't surprise me,
but I don't know.
Then we got this from end time. I'm just
trying to show you things that are going
on in this world where we're at right
now. Okay, this is from end times
headlines. The newsroom is changing. AI
reporters are now replacing humans. I've
seen this in other countries. It's
already happening in other countries.
We've been warned for years that AI
would eventually begin replacing human
workers. Now that future is arriving
inside the newsroom itself. Media
companies are increasingly experimenting
with AI generated voices, automated
production, synthetic personalities, and
AI assisted reporting. While some
traditional newsrooms positions are
disappearing and this raises a much
bigger question. What happens when the
people telling you what happened aren't
people anymore?
I'll tell you what happens. The
seven-year tribulation, because that's
coming very soon, you know, but this is
happening. I've seen new newscasts from
other uh countries in the world that are
using AI instead of humans, you know. I
guess it doesn't matter. The news
they're sharing is all fabricated
anyway. Might as well have AI presenting
it.
You know, this is what the elites have
in store for us in the last days. You
know, AI is everything
and they just, you know, I mean, do you
remember when we talked about this like
a year ago and I don't know if I ever I
probably didn't play the video clip. I
think I'll play it. Watch this video
clip.
>> Overall, I think there's quite a bit of
abdication of responsibility about
around like
what are we going to do as people's jobs
start being taken fairly aggressively.
Luckily, there's a massive population
drop coming, so [snorts]
maybe everything is just fate and it's
gonna work out. Okay,
>> there you go. And you know what she
said? Luckily, there's a massive
population drop coming. You're wondering
who this woman is. Well, her name is
Grimes. If you don't know her, she's a
Canadian pop star uh video maker,
Satanist, but she would probably admit
that. and she is Elon Musk's
ex-girlfriend. So, she's kind of in the
know of the global elitees plans, I'm
sure. But for her to say, "Luckily,
there's a massive population drop
coming." Well, there is. And the rapture
is going to take care of some of that
population drop, but the seven-year
tribulation is coming, and nobody's
hiding it anymore. They just say these
things out loud. It's amazing, really.
Then I'm going to share one more before
we get to Middle East stuff because
there's so much going on today around
this world. The world's getting crazier
by the day. But before we do that, I
want to share one more thing. Texas
Senate candidate James Telerico
has reportedly stated that Christianity,
Islam, and other religions are
essentially equal pathways to truth,
describing the world's faith traditions
as different paths surrounding the same
divine mystery.
He went even further saying that whether
someone calls that mystery God or
Yahweh, Allah, Nirvana or the great
spirit, there are ultimately different
pathways leading to the same fundamental
truth. This is what I call the lie from
the pit of hell. He has previously
described Christianity as the most
violent religion and claimed it has done
more damage to Islam than any other
faith. He has also said God is beyond
gender and asserted that the Bible is
silent regarding abortion. So this man
is literally running for the Senate in
Texas.
James Telerico,
we're living in dark times. You know, I
always have to say though, the the
gospel is getting brighter and brighter
and Jesus is shining brighter in this
world than ever.
All right, so Middle East news, it went
nuts again last night. uh US strikes
multiple Iranian tankers following an
attempted missile attacks on a US Navy
warship and the US strikes on Iranian
targets were going on last night. They
actually said that they destroyed five
Iranian tankers. You know, US Central
Command said that then Iran was
launching cluster munition missiles at
US bases in Jordan. again last night. Uh
the US military forces attacked and
destroyed five Iranian oil tankers after
the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps uh
tried to attack an American warship.
They said last night, US Central Command
said that. And they also said that in
the last week that they have destroyed
10 Iranian tankers. It's a lot of
tankers, man. 10 of them. Jordan
announced last night that Iran had
launched 20 ballistic missiles towards
it and 18 were intercepted and two fell
far from populated areas.
Uh the Iranian revolutionary guard
according to insider paper they said
last night that they had seized an
American submarine drone in the
strategic straight of Hormuz which
thrron has blockaded in the monthsl long
Middle East war. Quote, "The IRGC naval
forces captured one of the most modern,
unmanned, and smart submarines of the US
terrorist army at the entrance of the
straight of Hormuz in a complex
intelligence and operational action at
dawn today." They said this yesterday.
Did they? I think they did. I'm not
positive. Um I'm seeing conflicting
info, you know. I mean, I don't think
the US government is going to say,
"Yeah, they took one of our unmanned,
you know, drones or unmanned um
submarine drone." And I just don't think
they're going to admit that. But I think
they probably did take it. I saw some
footage that looked convincing. Some
footage. What else?
This was an insider paper early this
morning. Several vessels in the Gulf
region were on fire. A British maritime
agency reported today on Wednesday after
Iran said it had attacked 20 ships
trying to pass through the straight of
Hormuz. The latest round of attacks
comes amid a deadlock in the six-month
war. Iran has maintained its str its
strangle hold on the strategic straight
of Hormuz. As Washington continues
pressing its counterlockade of Iranian
ports. So, it goes on and on. I think
it's going to end up ramping up more
than we can even imagine soon, but we
will see. That's just my speculation.
Um,
what else?
End Times Headlines shared this which
was interesting because he said, "For
months we have repeatedly heard that
Iran had been severely weakened, its
military infrastructure devastated, its
economy collapsing, and its ability to
wage war dramatically diminished. And
yet, Iran continues to fire ballistic
missiles and drones at American military
positions across the Middle East. Iran
has recently launched attacks against US
assets in Jordan, Bahrain, and Iraq.
Jordan's military reported intercepting
Iranian ballistic missiles while Thran
has continued threatening even heavier
retaliation. US forces meanwhile have
continued striking Iranian military
infrastructure.
Yeah, I think we've been told for months
that, you know, they're they're a dying
army. Their army's gone. Their navy's
gone. We've been told this, but you know
what? They are proxies of China. Iran is
a proxy of China and Russia, I believe.
And that's why I just think that we're
in a situation where they're not they're
not just going to surrender and die
down, you know, you guys. Okay. I feel
like I'm taking my first breath of the
video. [sighs and gasps]
Anyway, go get a snack. Go get us a
snack, okay? And then come back. I want
those pretzels that have peanut butter
in the middle of them. Ever have those
little pretzel nugget things and they
got peanut butter in them? Those are
good.
Bubba News said Iran has launched more
than 20 missiles so far, direct hits in
Jordan and Iraq reported and he's talked
about last night.
And then this was breaking right before
um I hit record on this video and it
doesn't surprise us. We all know about
Pickax Mountain, but this was an insider
paper. A suspected underground Iranian
nuclear site has seen a surge in
construction this year. According to a
review of satellite imagery published by
the US analyst this morning, the deeply
buried site at Pickax Mountain is near
Natan's where Western intelligence
suspects Iran is building an undeclared
enrichment facility. Of course they are.
We know they are. You know the question
is are we ever going to take that out or
not? I don't know. We will see.
beginning of sorrows news on telegram
shared this quote from the minister of
foreign affairs of Iran Argotchi he said
after 47 years of sanctions the US went
to war with Iran on behalf of Israel the
fallout has been disastrous for America
including its standing worldwide after
failing to achieve its aims through
sanctions or war's
novel solution is more sanctions
seriously end of quote that's what what
he had to say. You know, that's what he
had to say. It looks like, here's some
speculation, okay? This is just
speculation, okay? So, take it for what
it's worth. It's out of my head and my
head can be a little weird sometimes,
but I almost feel like, you know,
they're saying that it looks like
America once again is send sending
refueling aircraft to Israel and looks
like they're getting ready to perhaps do
a strike on Iran again. And I'm
wondering if this is going to be a huge
strike cuz I this is the way I see it
playing out. Just total speculation.
I could see President Trump say look the
midterms are in two months. They're two
months from now. So I could see him
doing a huge strike like bad perhaps
destroying Pickax Mountain or some of
their nukes and then declaring victory
right away so that he can concentrate on
the election. And I don't see it all
going down that smoothly, but I'm
speculating that that could be what he's
thinking right now is I'm going to do a
massive strike, maybe with or without,
probably without Israel. I'm not sure,
but do a massive strike, declare a
victory, and then move on. You know,
doesn't that kind of make sense that
that could happen? And then he could
concentrate on the election, which, you
know, I can't imagine um you know, I I
don't want to get into politics. I hate
politics. All right, I'm just going to
go on to this. Oil prices could hit
$120, analysts are finding as Americans
absorb a hundred billion dollar fuel
hit. Uh Goldman Sachs is warning that
heightened attacks in the Persian Gulf
and Red Sea could blow could push the
global oil prices to $120 a barrel. Now,
I know as of this morning it hit $100 a
barrel again, but they're threatening
120. We'll see. We'll see. We trust the
Lord, right?
Then we got this. Um Bubba shared this
on Bubba News. He said, "A historic day
talked about yesterday. 12 countries
including the UK, France, and Canada
just announced a Jewish products ban on
products made in Samaria that employ
Palestinian workers in the West Bank."
These 12 nations tied this new ban
directly to Israel moving forward with
their E1 settlement. But this is much
more than just a ban. Bubba said, "Yes,
it is." And the 12 the countries were uh
Spain, France, Ireland, Poland, Iceland,
Finland, Canada, Norway, Sweden,
Portugal, Denmark, and the United
Kingdom. And they are all, you know,
saying no more trade with the West Bank,
you know,
and this is why, listen to this. French
President Mccron, British Prime Minister
Burnham, and Canadian Prime Minister
Carney said yesterday, Tuesday, that
Israeli settlements in the occupied West
Bank undermine prospects for a two-state
solution. You see, that's what this is
all about. They want a two-state
solution, and they think if Israel
builds quickly, ooh, beautiful,
beautiful birds flying away. uh they
think if you know they want the
two-state solution, thinking that if
that happens, you know, if if Israel
builds in Judea and Samaria, the West
Bank, that this will hurt the prospects
of a two-state solution, which they're
kind of obsessed with and have been for
a long time. They've never invited any
of the people into their own countries,
but uh not from that part of the world
anyway. In a joint statement, McCrron,
Vernham, and Carney said that a
two-state solution to the Israeli
Palestinian conflict was critical for
peace, stability, and security in the
Middle East and beyond.
How many times we going to hear peace
and security and stability, huh?
Yesterday, according to Insider Paper,
Putin and Trump had an extremely frank
phone call after US envoys visited.
Remember last week uh Jared and uh
Witkoff visited uh
visited Russia, but they said uh Russia
has no aggressive plans toward Europe.
Putin told Trump yesterday on this phone
call. So there you go. There you go. But
also insider paper had this. The world
must be prepared for a protracted
conflict between Russia and Ukraine. a
senior Pentagon official said Tuesday
according to Reuters.
So, uh, pray that that war ends. My
goodness, that's been my prayer because
I I love the people of Ukraine and the
people of Russia. The people are always
so different than the leaders, aren't
they? But pray for that war to end.
Earthquakes the last 24 hours there were
47 over 4.0 and 18 over 5.0. So, a lot
more than yesterday, which was one of
the lowest numbers I had ever ever said.
But yeah, 47 over 4.0, 18 over 5.0.
All right,
it is time for the question of the day.
Who is your favorite apostle and why?
Now, you know, I get to ask the
questions. I don't have to answer them,
but I have been answering them. It's so
hard to answer this one. Um, mine is
Paul or Peter, you know, but then all of
a sudden I think about James. I I'm
sorry, John. and and it's like ah
favorite apostle, but I'm going to say
Paul and Peter. Why? Well, they're just
they wrote amazing letters. They just
lived amazing lives. Uh Peter is just
he's fun to pick on and make fun of a
little bit. I love Peter. I loved his uh
you know, jumping in the water to walk
on the water with Jesus and then looking
down and sinking into the water. And I
love that he he was willing to fight for
Jesus so much. He wasn't a good sword
fighter because he he swung his sword
and he he just cut the guy's ear off.
You know, he he missed. But uh and then
Jesus healed the guy's ear. But I love
Peter and Paul. They're they're my two
favorite, but that could change. But
what are your who's your favorite
apostle and why? That's my question of
the day. Okay.
Now, we're going to move on to
Clown World. Okay.
And this is this is clowny. Here we go.
AI may soon enable humans to talk with
animals.
Okay. The idea of humans talking with
animals may move from the realm of
science fiction into reality with
scientific breakthroughs made by AI.
Researchers have employed large language
models to to decode complex patterns of
animal sounds and behaviors. Experts
speculate that a major breakthrough
enabling two-way communication may be
achieved by 2030 through initiatives
such as the collar doolittle prize.
AI has also shed light on interesting
animal communication protocols. You want
to talk to the animals. It's like Dr.
Dittle all over again. For example, AI
models suggest that bats use specific
signals for food, mating, and sleeping
positions. These conclusions were
derived from analyzing 15,000 bat calls.
It was also revealed that bats are able
to shift the tone of their calls
depending on whom they're addressing.
[laughter] Do you have interest in
talking to a bat? I have no I'm running
from a bat. Maybe I'm pretty good at
that. Talking to a bat? I It's just
clown world. I you know who wants to
talk to the I don't want to talk to the
animals. I I really don't because I know
every dog I've ever met in my life, all
they would say is I'm hungry. That's all
they would ever say, right? What else
would the dog say? You know, pet me,
scratch me, feed me. You know, I don't
need to talk to the animals. And cats,
you know what they'd say to me? Get away
from me, cuz cats are kind of snobby. I
like them, but they're snobby.
Anyway, that's just dumb humor. That's
just my dumb humor. Let's read a few
comments of the day, okay?
If I can find them.
Mark,
I always think I'm getting too old to go
out to kayak until I do it. Then
something out there gives me the
inspiration to keep going. Creation
shouts his praises in ways I can't
express. Someday I will thank him face
to face for everything like this. I love
that, Mark. Thank you. Yeah, nature had
no I miss, man. One of the things I miss
the most since I got neuropathy and Lyme
disease the last whatever seven years.
But one thing I missed the most is
hiking. Man, I loved to hike. I used to
hike year round and uh that stopped. So
one day I am going to hike with the Lord
in heaven. Okay, that's my plan. Lori,
please pray for me. I'm starting
chemotherapy and radiation. Love you all
so very much. God bless. Lori, we will
be praying for you. I know many now will
be praying for you as you go through
that. God has this too. Remember that he
has this.
Fernando, thank you, brother Tom, for
sharing this video. Let us all be
excited to meet Jesus in the clouds very
soon. We are seeing all these signs in
real time. I encourage everyone to keep
praying for one another and keep
preaching the word to usher more lost
souls into the kingdom. Salvation
belongs to our God who seats upon who
sits upon the throne. All glory belongs
to our God. Praise his holy name.
Marinatha. Amen brother. Thank you
Fernando. Beautiful.
Yesterday I asked for question of the
day what your favorite letter was in the
New Testament and Connor said, "My
favorite letter is probably Romans at
least right now. I struggle with worries
and doubt often, so I love the comfort
and reassur reassurance found in those
chapters. I agree, brother. Yeah, a lot
of people said Romans, but I think every
letter was said many times. I said
Galatians and I said right now because
it could change, but thank you,
Logan. Jesus Christ is the King of Kings
and the Lord of Lords and coming for his
bride soon. Amen, brother. Amen. He is
coming soon. We're living in the last
days. No one can convince me we're not.
I don't know when the rapture is going
to happen. I know one thing. Jesus said
when all these signs begin to happen and
all the signs he spoke of have begun to
happen, he said, "Look up for your
redemption drawth nigh or draws near."
And we're in that time period now. You
know, everything we were told to look
for, wars and rumors of wars and
pestilences and earthquakes and
everything is happening collectively
now. You know, you can if you take one
of the signs separately, you can say,
well, there's always been earthquakes.
Well, there's always been wars and
rumors of wars. But when you look at all
the signs collectively, you realize like
we're there. You know, and Israel is 78
years old. They're getting very old. And
we're waiting for Jesus right now. But
do you know him? Because if you don't
know him, it doesn't none of this
matters. You need to know what Jesus did
for you. You see, we all have a problem.
It's this little three-letter word
called sin. We're all sinners. We fall
short of the glory of God. Well, Tom,
you know, non-believers will say, "I'm
not an axe murderer." Because they look
at the word sin as like really bad sins.
You know what? All sins are equal. It's
all falling short of the glory of God.
God has this standard of perfection that
we can't live up to. And we all fall
short of it. And we need a payment for
our sin. And you know what? Since before
the foundation of the world, that
payment has always been declared to be
blood because that's how offensive sin
is to the most high God. Blood has to be
shed in order for sin to be removed. You
know, Hebrews 9:22 says, "Without the
shedding of blood, there is no remission
of sin." So, blood has to be shed. I
know it's graphic, but that's how
serious sin is to God. But God sent his
only begotten son Jesus that whoever
believes in him should not perish but
have everlasting life. He sent Jesus to
this world and Jesus came here from
heaven to pay for that sin problem we
have with his blood, God blood. And
that's why Jesus blood that he shed is
the once-forall payment for sin. You
know, it's so amazing that he came here
and he walked this world and his
performance was perfect because he's
completely God and completely man in the
same body. His performance was perfect.
He loved on people. He did miracles. He
was teaching incredible truth through
parables, but he came here to die on
that cross. So, don't let anyone tell
you that lie from the pit of hell when
they say, "Well, Jesus was a good and
wise teacher, but he had a horrible
ending." No. Jesus left heaven to come
here to die in that cross to shed his
blood to rescue you and me from our sin
problem. Well, how do we get rescued?
Well, once we understand what Jesus did
and how much we need a payment for the
sins we do, you say to Jesus, "Jesus, I
admit I'm a sinner. I know I'm a sinner.
I know I'm not perfect. I sin all the
time. I think things I shouldn't think.
I've done things I'm ashamed of. But I
now believe that you, the God of all
eternity, made an appearance on earth to
pay for my sins with your blood. I I
believe in your atoning blood. I have
faith in your blood that it will wash me
white as snow and completely remove my
entire sin problem, past, present, and
future sins. And Jesus, I believe that
you went to that cross. You were nailed
to that cross. You shed that blood. You
died. You were buried. And you rose
again. You are the savior of the world
and I need a savior. I now realize Lord,
I need a savior. So now I'm believing in
your atoning blood and in your gospel,
your good news, your death, your burial,
your resurrection. And at that moment of
belief, do you know what happens? You're
born again. God places the Holy Spirit
inside of you. You have new life. You're
a new creation in Christ Jesus, seated
in heavenly places. You're sealed until
the day of redemption. And he won't let
you out of the palm of his hand. Jesus
wants to spend forever and ever and ever
with you. What are you going to do with
that? Because you know what? I'm going
to tell you something right now, and
this is a fact. At the moment of
conception, you became an eternal being.
You will be somewhere for eternity. And
there's two sides to the coin. It's
either being with Jesus forever and ever
in paradise or being separated from God
forever and ever in a place described of
in the Bible as weeping and wailing and
nashing of teeth. Tom, I don't like when
you tell me if I don't believe in Jesus,
I'm going to go to hell. Well, I'm just
the messenger. I didn't, you know, I
didn't create the universe. God did. You
know, God doesn't want anyone to perish
and go to hell. He wants all to come to
repentance. He wants all to believe in
his only begotten son, Jesus.
You know, it's a serious decision you
have to make. It's the most important
decision of your life. And unlike that
guy who's running for the Senate who
says there are many paths to heaven, no,
Jesus is the way, the truth, and the
life. These are his words. No one comes
to the father except through me. It's
the only way to heaven is Jesus. So
that's decision you are left with now is
the most important decision of your
life. What are you going to do with
this? Go talk to Jesus. If this sounds
like truth, run to Jesus now. Don't put
it off. Run now.
You know, because if you keep saying,
"Well, I don't want to have to believe
this. I don't believe this." You will
face him one day on judgment day, and
you will be kneeling before him knowing
you're in the presence of God, and he'll
send you off to hell. And I, my
goodness, that just is terrifying. I
wouldn't wish that on my worst enemy,
honestly.
Right. In my prayer time this morning, I
said a prayer for every single person
who would watch this video, and that
includes you. So, like it or not, you
have been prayed for. And if we're not
raptured today, and you know me, I think
today, why not? It's perfectly good day
for the rapture, but it's not up to me.
But if not today, God willing, I will
see you guys tomorrow. I love you guys.
Oh Jesus, [music]
savior,
master, [music]
creator.
You're the alpha.
Oh, [music]
you're the king of kings.